A Guide to the William Byrd Community House Archives, 1946-1986
Virginia Commonwealth University, James Branch Cabell Library
- Oregon Hill Project 1954-1979
  - Oregon Hill Home Improvement Cash Expenditure (Box-folder 15.9)
  - Oregon Hill Home Improvement Council (Box-folder 15.10)
  - Oregon Hill Home Improvement Council-Bank Statements 1973 (Box-folder 15.11)
  - Oregon Hill Home Improvement Council-Bank Statements 1976 (Box-folder 15.12)
  - Oregon Hill Home Improvement Council-Bank Statements 1977 (Box-folder 15.13)
  - Oregon Hill Home Improvement Council-Inventory 1973 (Box-folder 15.14)
  - Oregon Hill Home Improvement Council Meeting Minutes 1977-1978 (Box-folder 15.15)
  - Oregon Hill Home Improvement Council-Notes 1975 (Box-folder 15.16)
  - Oregon Hill Home Improvement Council-Receipts 1977 (Box-folder 15.17)
  - Oregon Hill Home Improvement Council-Revenue 1973 (Box-folder 15.18)
  - Oregon Hill Home Imporovement Council-Support and Revenue 1973 (Box-folder 15.19)
  - Oregon Hill Housing-Planning and Ideas 1975 (Box-folder 15.20)
  - Oregon Hill Inter-Agency Services (Box-folder 15.21)
  - Oregon Hill Landlord-Property Information 1973 (Box-folder 15.22)
  - Oregon Hill Neighborhood Council (Box-folder 15.23)
  - Oregon Hill Neighborhood Council 1954 (Box-folder 15.24)
  - Oregon Hill Neighborhood Council 1971-1974 (Box-folder 15.25)
  - Oregon Hill Neighborhood Meeting Flyer 1975 (Box-folder 15.26)
  - Oregon Hill Neighborhood Planning Study-Techinical Report 1976 (Box-folder 15.27)
  - Oregon Hill Neighborhood Publicity 1973 (Box-folder 15.28)
  - Oregon Hill News 1977 (Box-folder 15.29)
  - Oregon Hill Newsletter 1972-1975 (Box-folder 15.30)
  - Oregon Hill Newsletter 1976 (Box-folder 15.31)
  - Oregon Hill Newsletter 1977 (Box-folder 15.32)
  - Oregon Hill-Project Area Committee 1975-1977 (Box-folder 15.33)
  - Oregon Hill Summer Home Repair Project 1973 (Box-folder 15.34)
  - Other Community Organizations Outside Oregon Hill (Box-folder 15.35)
  - Petition for Oregon Hill Home Repairs (Box-folder 15.36)
  - Social Work Research Paper on Oregon Hill 1978 (Box-folder 15.37)
  - Survey Conducted on Problems of the Oregon Hill Community 1971 (Box-folder 15.38)
- Correspondence 1969-1983
  - Correspondence 1969-1970 (Box-folder 16.1)
  - Correspondence 1971 (Box-folder 16.2)
  - Correspondence 1975-1976 (Box-folder 16.3)
  - Correspondence 1977-1979 (Box-folder 16.4)
  - Correspondence-In 1975 (Box-folder 16.5)
  - Correspondence 1977 (Box-folder 16.6)
  - Correspondence-In 1978 (Box-folder 16.7)
  - Correspondence-In 1979 (Box-folder 16.8)
  - Correspondence-In 1982 (Box-folder 16.9)
  - Correspondence-In 1983 (Box-folder 16.10)
  - Correspondence-Out 1975 (Box-folder 16.11)
  - Correspondence-Out 1975-1976 (Box-folder 17.1)
  - Correspondence-Out 1977 (Box-folder 17.2)
  - Correspondence-Out 1978 (Box-folder 17.3)
  - Correspondence-Out 1979 (Box-folder 17.4)
  - Correspondence-Out 1982 (Box-folder 17.5)
  - Correspondence-Out 1983 (Box-folder 17.6)
  - Correspondence to Roy Reynolds 1978-1979 (Box-folder 17.7)
  - Correspondence-Xerox Corporation 1976 (Box-folder 17.8)
  - Opportunities Industrialization Center-Correspondence 1981 (Box-folder 17.9)
  - United Neighborhood Centers of America-Correspondence 1980-1981 (Box-folder 17.10)
- Reports 1946-1984
  - Annual Reports 1946-1979 (Box-folder 18.1-18.29)
  - Boys Supervisor's Report 1971 (Box-folder 18.30)
  - Dental Health Report 1971 (Box-folder 18.31)
  - Director's Monthly Reports 1962-1964 (Box-folder 18.32)
  - Director's Monthly Reports 1966 (Box-folder 18.33)
  - Directors Monthly Reports 1967-1968 (Box-folder 18.34)
  - Director's Monthly Reports 1969 (Box-folder 18.35)
  - Director's Monthly Reports 1975 (Box-folder 18.36)
  - File Report on Accident 1976 (Box-folder 18.37)
  - Gym and Field Reports 1970 (Box-folder 18.38)
  - Gym and Fiel Reports 1971 (Box-folder 18.39)
  - Law Enforcement Assistance Administration-Reports (Box-folder 18.40)
  - Monthly Reports 1965-1984 (Box-folder 19.1-19.16)
  - Monthly and Annual Reports 1967-1968 (Box-folder 19.17)
  - Nursery School Report 1971 (Box-folder 20.1)
  - Pre-Teen Report 1971 (Box-folder 20.2)
  - Report on Child Care (Box-folder 20.3)
  - Report on Examination 1972 (Box-folder 20.4)
  - Report on Examination 1973 (Box-folder 20.5)
  - Report on Examination 1974 (Box-folder 20.6)
  - Report on Examination 1975 (Box-folder 20.7)
  - Report on Examination 1976 (Box-folder 20.8)
  - Report on Examination 1977 (Box-folder 20.9)
  - Report on Examination 1978 (Box-folder 20.10)
  - Report on the Randolph Plan 1972 (Box-folder 20.11)
  - Reports 1971 (Box-folder 20.12)
  - Research Project- Slum and Blight (Box-folder 20.13)
  - Staff Reports 1970 (Box-folder 20.14)
  - Staff Reports 1976 (Box-folder 20.15)
  - State Corporation Report 1961 (Box-folder 20.16)
  - The Comprehensive Interagency Diagnostic and Prescriptive Center-4th Annual Report 1983-1984 (Box-folder 20.17)
  - Tot Lot Report 1971 (Box-folder 20.18)
  - Virginia Council on Social Welfare 1961 (Box-folder 20.19)
  - Virginia Council on Social Welfare 1962 (Box-folder 20.20)
  - Virginia Council on Social Welfare 1963 (Box-folder 20.21)
  - Virginia Council on Social Welfare 1964 (Box-folder 20.22)
  - Virginia Council on Social Welfare 1965 (Box-folder 20.23)
  - Virginia Council on Social Welfare 1966 (Box-folder 20.24)
  - Youth Employment Project Reports (Box-folder 20.25)
- Budgets 1949-1981
  - Budget 1959-1980 (Box-folder 21.1-21.25)
  - Budget Forms 1965 (Box-folder 21.26)
  - Budget Manual 1964 (Box-folder 21.27)
  - Cash Receipts and Disbursements 1949-1971 (Box-folder 21.28)
  - Child Care Finances 1981 (Box-folder 22.1)
  - Federal Income Taxes 1966-1969 (Box-folder 22.2)
  - Finance Committee 1974 (Box-folder 22.3)
  - Finances 1978 (Box-folder 22.4)
  - Finances 1980 (Box-folder 22.5)
  - Financial Statements 1979 (Box-folder 22.6)
  - Financial Statements 1980 (Box-folder 22.7)
  - Law Enforcement Assistance Administration-Budget and Forms 1978 (Box-folder 22.8)
  - Money Receipts 1973 (Box-folder 22.9)
  - Monthly Budgets 1975 (Box-folder 22.10)
  - Payment Vouchers 1980 (Box-folder 22.11)
  - Program Budget 1978 (Box-folder 22.12)
  - Program Budget 1981 (Box-folder 22.13)
  - Receipts (January-September) 1975 (Box-folder 22.14)
  - Receipts (October-December) 1975 (Box-folder 23.1)
  - Receipts (January-December) 1980 (Box-folder 23.2)
  - Receipts and Disbursements Journal 1973 (Box-folder 23.3)
  - Taxes 1959 (Box-folder 23.4)
  - Taxes 1962 (Box-folder 23.5)
  - Taxes 1963 (Box-folder 23.6)
  - Taxes 1971 (Box-folder 23.7)
  - Taxes 1972 (Box-folder 23.8)
  - Taxes 1973 (Box-folder 23.9)
  - Tax Return 1960 (Box-folder 23.10)
  - Tax Return 1965 (Box-folder 23.11)
- Slides of Housing Projects